<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Fil B - Public Hub</title>
    <link>https://filbezerianos.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Fil B - Public Hub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://filbezerianos.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>The Dominant Strategy in Game Theory and AI</title>
      <link>https://filbezerianos.com/posts/ai-dominant-strategy/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://filbezerianos.com/posts/ai-dominant-strategy/</guid>
      
      <description>One of the most classic examples of Game Theory is the Prisoner&amp;rsquo;s Dilemma, which illustrates the conflict between individual rationality and collective rationality.
In this article, we will explore what game theory acn teach us about AI adoption and how the dominant strategy may lead to a race to the bottom.
The Prisoner&amp;rsquo;s Dilemma The Prisoner&amp;rsquo;s Dilemma involves two prisoners suspected of committing a crime together. They are interrogated in separate rooms and cannot communicate with each other.</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A.I. = Accelerate Inefficiencies</title>
      <link>https://filbezerianos.com/posts/ai-challenges-accelerator/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://filbezerianos.com/posts/ai-challenges-accelerator/</guid>
      
      <description>AI is transforming the business and technology landscape, promising efficiency, innovation and better decision-making. However, for organisations already struggling with technology-business misalignment, structural and operational inefficiencies and lack of governance, AI will accelerate and amplify these challenges.
In this article, we will explore how AI can accelerate some challenges currently faced by the organisations and outline some approaches to avoid and address these.
Challenges There are multiple gaps and inefficiencies that AI can amplify and accelerate if these are not considered and addressed during the adoption journey.</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Blending AI and Product Management</title>
      <link>https://filbezerianos.com/posts/ai-product-management/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://filbezerianos.com/posts/ai-product-management/</guid>
      
      <description>The introduction of AI into product development represents a transformative shift in how products are developed, managed and evolved. AI product phases are integrating into various stages of the product management lifecycle. Successfully aligning and integrating the AI product management phases into product management lifecycle, will accelerate the pace of innovation and introduce new capabilities, but may also introduce new challenges.
In addition, the role of Product Manager must evolve alongside the changes posed by AI to ensure that they understand the potential, limitations and risks of AI.</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Behind the Scences</title>
      <link>https://filbezerianos.com/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://filbezerianos.com/about/</guid>
      
      <description>Passionate about solving complex challenges and empowering teams to reach their full potential.
As a professional I stand at the intersection of technology and business, specialising in designing, developing and implementing solutions to drive tangible business outcomes. I work with industry-leading enterprises and exceptionally talented individuals to transform technical potential into substantial business value and reshaping entire organisations.
I am deeply committed to continuous learning - for a list of courses and certifications visit Credentials, my Credly profile or LinkedIn.</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Learning Continuum</title>
      <link>https://filbezerianos.com/credentials/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://filbezerianos.com/credentials/</guid>
      
      <description>I am continuously striving to expand my knowledge and skills, acquiring a diverse array of academic qualifications and professional certifications. I view each step in my educational journey not just as a milestone, but a foundation for further growth.
From prestigious universities to industry-leading certifications, the credentials below represent my pursuit and deep commitment to lifelong learning.
Institution Subject Cornell University AI Strategy, eCornell MIT Technology and Innovation Acceleration Program, MIT xPro MIT Digital Transformation: Platform Strategies for Success, MIT Sloan Executive Education MIT Organisational Design for Digital Transformation, MIT Sloan School of Management Columbia Business School Digital Strategies for Business: Leading the Next Generation Enterprise City University of London Risk Management in Banking and Finance Imperial College MSc In Electrical Engineering, Control Systems Throughout my career, I have pursued and achieved multiple technical and business certifications, consistently seeking opportunities to expand my skills.</description>
      
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
