<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Fil B - Public Hub</title>
    <link>https://filbezerianos.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Fil B - Public Hub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 16:14:29 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://filbezerianos.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Behind the Scences</title>
      <link>https://filbezerianos.com/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://filbezerianos.com/about/</guid>
      
      <description>Passionate about solving complex challenges and empowering teams to reach their full potential.
As a professional I stand at the intersection of technology and business, specialising in designing, developing and implementing solutions to drive tangible business outcomes. I work with industry-leading enterprises and exceptionally talented individuals to transform technical potential into substantial business value and reshaping entire organisations.
I am deeply committed to continuous learning - for a list of courses and certifications visit Credentials, my Credly profile or LinkedIn.</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Learning Continuum</title>
      <link>https://filbezerianos.com/credentials/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://filbezerianos.com/credentials/</guid>
      
      <description>I am continuously striving to expand my knowledge and skills, acquiring a diverse array of academic qualifications and professional certifications. I view each step in my educational journey not just as a milestone, but a foundation for further growth.
From prestigious universities to industry-leading certifications, the credentials below represent my pursuit and deep commitment to lifelong learning.
Institution Subject Cornell University AI Strategy, eCornell MIT Technology and Innovation Acceleration Program, MIT xPro MIT Digital Transformation: Platform Strategies for Success, MIT Sloan Executive Education MIT Organisational Design for Digital Transformation, MIT Sloan School of Management Columbia Business School Digital Strategies for Business: Leading the Next Generation Enterprise City University of London Risk Management in Banking and Finance Imperial College MSc In Electrical Engineering, Control Systems Throughout my career, I have pursued and achieved multiple technical and business certifications, consistently seeking opportunities to expand my skills.</description>
      
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
